https://barefootgolf.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Skip to content
1-866-638-4818Facebook page opens in new windowTwitter page opens in new windowInstagram page opens in new windowLinkedin page opens in new windowMail page opens in new windowGet a Quick Quote Quick QuoteBook Tee Times Online Book Tee Times
Home GolfGolf CoursesNorman Course Love Course Fazio Course Dye Course Awards
InstructionDyer Golf Academy Greg Norman Champions Golf Academy
InfoGreen Fees Tee Times Range FAQ News and Events Mission Statement
Stay and PlayLodging at Barefoot ResortBarefoot Resort Golf Villas Yacht Club Villas North Beach Plantation Courtyard Marriott
PackagesStay and Play Popular Golf Packages Golf Package Specials Tee Times Only Personalized Quick Quote What’s Included
Travel InfoCheck-in Instructions FAQ Myrtle Beach Flights Golf Club Shipping
Resort InfoClubhousesResort Dye
Getting HereDriving Directions Flights to Myrtle Beach
Real EstateOwn Rent
History Community Area Info
MembershipBecoming a MemberBarefoot Resort & Golf Membership Snowbird Membership Program How to Enroll Frequently Asked Questions Membership Contact Form
Current MembersMember-Guest Rates Calendar of Events The Egret Newsletter Handicap Lookup Membership Blog
MeetingsMeetings and Event Services Facilities Activities Request Form Tournament Services Event/Outing Food Menu
WeddingsResort Function/Menu Dye Function/Menu Request Form
ContactContact Form Staff Careers
Privacy PolicyYou are here:HomePrivacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for barefootgolf.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 843-390-3236 or via email.
Go to Top
Barefoot COVID-19 UpdateLearn More
+ +
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy policy
